hellomagazine.com 2019-12-10

# Privacy policy| hellomagazine.com

### HELLO! Ltd Privacy Policy 

In accordance with current data protection regulations (Data Protection Act & GDPR EU 679/2016), Users, being those persons accessing the Web Site and/or sending a request or email to the Web Site or completing a Web Site form or registration process, are informed that any personal data provided through or to the Web Site may be processed by HOLA, S.L (hereinafter, the Entity), as Data Controller and/or by HELLO! Ltd, as Data Processor of the Entity (hereinafter, the Data Processor).

HOLA, S.L. (the Entity), is a legal entity and its registered office address is Calle Miguel Ángel, 1, 28010, Madrid, Spain and VAT number ES-B86326360

HELLO! LTD (the Data Processor), is a legal entity and its registered office address is Wellington House, 69-71 Upper Ground, London SE1 9PQ, UK and VAT number GB-480771530.

For the purposes of our data protection policy, the contact telephone number is 0207 667 8700 and the contact email is [contact@hellomagazine.com](mailto:contact@hellomagazine.com)

We hold the following data:

  * Identity
  * Postal or electronic addresses and contact telephone number (where applicable)
  * Country of residence
  * Economic and transaction data including payment card data (HELLO! subscribers only).

All data has been provided to the Entity by Users through forms available at hellomagazine.com. It is the responsibility of Users to notify the Entity of any modifications or changes to this data.

At hellomagazine.com, we will use your data to carry out some of the following activities:

  * Replying to requests for information.
  * Managing the process of registration of the User.
  * Managing the online subscription process.
  * Managing the sending of the newsletter.
  * Providing Users with information and contents requested.
  * Providing Users with ads, information, offers and/or promotions of the Entity or any third parties.
  * Fulfilling User requests for products and services.
  * Customising ads and content.
  * Improving our products, services and content, and conducting research in order to do so.

In addition, should the User provide the Web Site or the Entity with an email address or any other means of electronic communication, the User expressly authorizes the Entity to use such means as a way of communicating with him/her in order to reply to his/her requests and/or consultations, to provide him/her with information or news of the Entity and to inform him/her of any relevant changes which are made on or to the Web Site. However, the User may object to the use of his contact email for commercial purposes by means of the corresponding box in the respective form for collecting data. In addition, the User retains the right to revoke such consent at any time by the [clicking here](https://www.hellomagazine.com/unsubscribe/)

Based on the information provided by the User and their navigation history, hellomagazine.com creates a User profile that allows us to personalize information, announcements, etc. while browsing our Web Site. In no case will we make decisions based on that profile.

User’s personal data that HELLO! Ltd collects through the different contact and / or information collection forms will be kept as long as deletion is not requested by the User. The data provided by our subscribers will be kept as long as the commercial relationship between the parties is maintained with regards to any minimum legal requirements.

Personal data will also be kept to respond to issues that arise, to solve problems, to make improvements, to activate new services and will also meet legal requirements. This may mean that we retain your personal data for a reasonable period of time even after you have stopped using our products or website. After this period, your personal data will be deleted from all Data Controller and Data Processor systems.

We process data in the following way:

**DATA PROCESSING:**

  1. Management of contact requests through the website
  2. Management, analysis and segmentation of web users and panelists
  3. Managing subscriptions in the print edition of HELLO Magasine (Data Controller: HELLO Ltd.)

**BASIS OF LEGITIMACY**

  1. Consent of the user in his capacity as interested party
  2. Consent of the user in his capacity as interested party
  3. Execution of subscription contract between the subscriber and HELLO Ltd

HELLO! Ltd will never share your personal data with any third-party company, except in the case that you have expressly authorized us to do so. We may share your personal data with a third-party auditing organisation (ABC) so they can verify aggregated statistics about circulation and usage of our products or review our policies, processes and procedures for compliance with relevant standards. You can view their privacy policy by following this [link](https://www.abc.org.uk/privacy-policy/)

We may also provide your personal data to Public Administration bodies and competent authorities in those cases that HELLO! Ltd receives a legal request, or in acting in good faith, we consider that such action is necessary to comply with a legal process, such as to answer any claim; or to protect the rights of HELLO! Ltd or its customers and the general public.

Anyone has the right to obtain confirmation on whether HELLO! Ltd is processing their personal data. In particular, Users can request the right of access to their personal data. Likewise, Users may request the right to correct inaccurate data or, if appropriate, request its deletion when, for example, the data is no longer necessary for the purposes that it was collected. In addition, in certain circumstances, the User may request the limitation of the processing of their data, or their right to oppose the processing of their data. HELLO! Ltd will stop processing the data, except for compelling legitimate reasons, or the exercise or defense of possible claims or in those exceptions established in the applicable regulations.

Likewise, we inform you that you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time, without affecting the legality of the treatment based on the consent prior to its withdrawal.

The User is also informed that at any time he / she can exercise the aforementioned rights by writing to us using the contact data for either 'Data Controller' and / or 'Data Processor' at the top of this HELLO! Ltd Privacy Policy, attaching a copy of a personal identification document. You will also have the right to file a claim with the corresponding Data Protection Authorities for the 'Data Controller' and / or 'Data Processor', especially if you feel you have not gained a satisfactory response.

I. Data Protection Authority applicable to the Data Controller (HOLA, SL):

**Spanish Agency for Data Protection (Agencia de Protección de Datos)**

<http://www.agpd.es/portalwebAGPD/CanalDelCiudadano/index-ides-idphp.php>

II. Data Protection Authority applicable to the Data Processor (HELLO Ltd):

**ICO - Information Commissioner's office**

<https://ico.org.uk/concerns/>

During your visit to the website hellomagazine.com, a cookie is placed on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser preferences allow it. For more details on the purposes of this, please [click here ](https://www.hellomagazine.com/cookies.html)to access our Cookie’s Policy.

HELLO! Ltd adopts the security levels required by UK and European regulations in force in data protection taking into account the state of the art, the costs of application and the nature, scope, context and purposes of the treatment described, as well as the risks of probability and severity variables for their rights and freedoms as a person.

The protection of personal data of children is very important, for this reason, access and use of the portal to unauthorized minors is prohibited. As established by the data protection regulations, the consent of parents or guardians will be necessary for the processing of personal data of children under 16 years of age. HELLO! Ltd cannot be held responsible for minors using the website and as such it is the responsibility of parents/guardians to control or assist minors in accessing this website. In any case, any data collection will always be done with the express consent of parents/guardians.

Occasionally, HELLO! Ltd may make modifications or corrections to its Privacy Policy. Please check this section regularly to see what changes have been made and how they may affect you.

This Privacy Policy is for users of hellomagazine.com website and subscribers to HELLO! Magazine (print edition). It provides all the necessary information in an easily accessible way so that the type of data that hellomagazine.com and HELLO! LTD hold on users and clients, the purposes pursued, the rights that data protection regulations allow you and how to exercise those rights is set out in a clear and concise manner. Therefore, by providing consent to your personal data and / or with the beginning of a commercial relationship with HELLO! Ltd, we consider that you acknowledge and accept the processing of your personal data as described in this policy. This personal information will only be used for the purposes for which you have provided it and for what national or regional regulations enable us to do.

For full details of our Subscription Term and Conditions, please [click here](https://www.hellomagazine.com/subscription-terms-conditions.html). In the case of subscriptions to digital editions of HELLO! Magazine and HFM - HELLO! Fashion Monthly we inform you that the Data Controllers on the processing of your data will be the management entities of the online content download platforms. Consequently, HELLO! Ltd does not assume any responsibility for the processing of your data made by each online content management platform. You should carefully read the privacy policy of the content management platform of your choice.

It is noted that the Data Controller of the 'Subscriptions' section refers to print subscriptions to HELLO! Magazine and is HELLO LTD.

In any case, we must warn you that a refusal on your part to provide certain requested information during the subscription process could hinder the development of the contractual relationship between the parties with the possibility of the cancellation or termination of your subscription.

To cancel your subscription to our newsletter and alerts go to [this page](https://www.hellomagazine.com/unsubscribe/)

If you have any questions regarding this section of the hellomagazine.com Privacy Policy for Users and Customers of HELLO! Ltd, please contact the company at the address above or by emailing [contact@hellomagazine.com](mailto:contact@hellomagazine.com)

These Conditions will be governed at all times by the provisions of UK and European legislation on the protection of personal data and privacy.
